Turkey Press Broadside Collection M1736
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Turkey Press broadside collection
1975-2009
M1736
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
35.0 Items 1 portfolio
Broadsides feature contemporary poetry in a variety of formats and sizes.
Turkey Press.
Biographical/Historical Note
Harry Reese founded Turkey Press in 1974 when he was a graduate student at Brown University. A year later, he returned to Berkeley, California, and in 1977, with Sandra Liddell Reese as his partner, moved to Isla Vista, north of Santa Barbara. Harry Reese teaches book art, print, papermaking, and media ecology classes at the University of California, Santa Barbara.
Conditions Governing Access Note
Open for research; material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Turkey Press, 2010. Accession 2010-019.
Scope and Contents Note
1 portfolio of 35 pieces. These broadsides feature contemporary poetry in a variety of formats and sizes.
Turkey Press.
- Harry Reese, "Getting Full", 1975 (Item 1)
- Robert Pinsky, "The Time of Year, The Time of Day", 1975 (Item 2)
- Michael Hogan, "Progress", 1977 (Item 3)
- Rabindranath Tagore, "The Merchant Child", 1978 (Item 4)
- Gerald Locklin, "Beer", 1979 (Item 5)
- Bob Brandts, "Down Town Santa Barbara", 1979 (Item 6)
- Bob Brandts, "Trout Club Post Card", 1979 (Item 7)
- David Roberts, "informal rambling commentary on reality and life", 1979 (Item 8)
- Alan Watts, "you discover who you are", 1980 (Item 9)
- Thoreau, "Selections from Walden", 1980 (Item 10)
- Michael Hannon, "Desire", 1981 (Item 11)
- Jared Dawson, "Death of a Romantic", 1981 (Item 12)
- Tom Clark, "I drift...", 1981 (Item 13)
- Bern Porter, "ME", 1982 (Item 14)
- Bern Porter, "American Strange (Mohawk Superfine)", 1983 (Item 15)
- Bern Porter, "Time", 1983 (Item 16)
- Edwin Honig, "History of the Book", 1983 (Item 17)
- Edwin Honig, "God", 1983 (Item 18)
- Miachael Hannon, "Literature and Friendship", 1983 (Item 19)
- David Ossman, "Third Mesa", 1985 (Item 20)
- David Ossman, "An Autobozographical Evening", 1985 (Item 21)
- Octavio Paz, "Altar", 1986 (Item 22)
- Michael Hannon, "Harpoon for the Dreamer", 1986 (Item 23)
- David Ossman, "The Last Day of Summer & A Response", 1987 (Item 24)
- Harry Reese, "Sixpointoneoctoberone", 1987 (Item 25)
- David Ossman, "Santa Fe Road", 1988 (Item 26)
- Michael Hannon, "ars poetica", 1989 (Item 27)
- James Laughlin, "The Lady Bug", 1994 (Item 28)
- Marshall McLuhan, "The Message of Print and Typography", 1994 (Item 29)
- Marshall McLuhan, "typography is not only a technology", 1994 (Item 30)
- Michael Hannon, "The Good Marriage", 1995 (2010?) (Item 31)
- Laozi, translated by Tom Meyer, "Daode Jing", 2005 (Item 32)
- Ezra Pound, "Canto XIII", 2005 (Item 33)
- Geoffrey Young, "Forget Regrets", 2007 (Item 34)
- Michael Hannon, "after and hour...", "Not so much by light" (2 sheets), 2009 (Item 35)